<?xml version= "1.0"?><rss version= "2.0"><channel><item><title>Free Unlimited Worldwide Phone Calls</title><description>Download Skype now and enjoy a whole months worth of calls to landlines and even mobiles in over 40 countries free for a limited time.            </description><link>http://clkuk.tradedoubler.com/click?p(224237)a(104497)</link></item>
<item><title>Free Roboform Form Filler &amp; Login Manager</title><description>RoboForm is an award-winning automated password manager and web form filler with some serious Artificial Intelligence!                                                </description><link>http://www.roboform.com/dist/affs/AiRoboForm-fcuk1.exe</link></item>
<item><title>Free Malwarebytes Malware Remover</title><description>Remove all those nasty malware programs from your PC with the best tool around – simply click ‘free download' to get this great app.</description><link>http://www.dpbolvw.net/click-990216-11125352</link></item>
<item><title>Free Norton Online Family Protection</title><description>Help protect your children while they surf the web with this handy freebie courtesy of Argos that'll monitor and limit their internet usage.</description><link>http://www.kqzyfj.com/click-990216-10617517?url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.argos.co.uk%2Fstatic%2FArgosPromo3%2FincludeName%2Fnorton-anti-virus.htm%3FstoreId%3D10151</link></item>
<item><title>Free 5GB Amazon Cloud Drive</title><description>Amazon is offering 5GB of online ‘cloud' storage to store all your files, from photos, to documents, and more – entirely free forever.</description><link>http://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/feature.html/?ie=UTF8&camp=1634&creative=6738&docId=1000655803&linkCode=ur2&tag=a4fu-21</link></item>
<item><title>Free 2GB Mozy Cloud Storage</title><description>Sign up to Mozy for 2GB of cloud storage and automatically backup your PC offsite - plus file sync and share with other PC's too!</description><link>http://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-990216-10966639</link></item>
<item><title>Free Dragonica MMORPG Game</title><description>Join the colourful fantasy world of Dragonica with millions of players worldwide and discover action packed adventures in this vibrant free MMORPG.</description><link>http://track.webgains.com/click.html?wglinkid=71213&wgprogramid=2424&wgcampaignid=78996&wgtarget=http://en.dragonica.gpotato.eu/ad/</link></item>
<item><title>Free Farmerama Online Game</title><description>Free Farmerama Online Game
Join millions of others and set up your very own farm growing and harvesting crops, raising animals, delivering orders… and more!</description><link>http://www.awin1.com/cread.php?s=254499&v=3277&q=116828&r=3927</link></item>
<item><title>Free PC Kindle eReader</title><description>Get access to hundreds of free books (and premium ones too!) on your desktop PC or laptop with this free Kindle app from Amazon.</description><link>http://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/feature.html?ie=UTF8&ref_=kcp_pc_mkt_lnd&docId=1000423913#?ie=UTF8&tag=a4fu-21&linkCode=ur2&camp=1634&creative=19450</link></item>
<item><title>Free HD Desktop Wallpapers</title><description>A wide selection of beautiful and stunning photos in a huge variety of resolutions suitable even for even the biggest screen.</description><link>http://interfacelift.com/wallpaper/downloads/date/hdtv/</link></item>
<item><title>Free Cut the Rope Online Game</title><description>Cutesy game where the objective is to manoeuvre a piece of candy into the mouth of super adorable green monster called Om Nom.</description><link>http://www.cuttherope.ie/</link></item>
<item><title>Free Secunia PSI Software Updater</title><description>Fantastic free software that ensures the programs installed on your PC are secure by downloading and installing the latest patches and fixes for them.</description><link>http://secunia.com/vulnerability_scanning/personal/</link></item>
<item><title>Free DC Universe Online Game</title><description>Become an hero or a villain as you assume extraordinary powers in this fast paced action adventure experience now free on the PC and the PS3.</description><link>http://www.dcuniverseonline.com/</link></item>
<item><title>Free Battlefield Online Game</title><description>Based on the Battlefield 2 games this first person shooter will allow up to 32 players to fight against each other, in helicopters, fighter jets, tanks, and more!</description><link>http://battlefield.play4free.com/en/</link></item>
<item><title>Free Team Fortress 2 Online Game</title><description>One of the most popular online action games of all time, and constantly updated, with new game modes, maps, equipment and, most importantly, hats!</description><link>http://www.teamfortress.com/freetoplay/</link></item>
<item><title>Free Angry Birds Online Game</title><description>You can now play the mobile phenomenon in your internet browser! YaY!</description><link>http://chrome.angrybirds.com/?version=standard&renderer=canvas</link></item>
<item><title>Free Avast! Antivirus</title><description>Download the latest version of one of the world's most popular antivirus programs and enjoy complete protection from viruses.</description><link>http://www.avast.com/free-antivirus-download</link></item>
<item><title>Free Harms Way Xbox 360 Game</title><description>Action packed racing where drivers and snipers work together to take out the competition - download this highly rated game from the Xbox Marketplace now</description><link>http://marketplace.xbox.com/en-GB/Product/Harms-Way/66acd000-77fe-1000-9115-d80258410a70</link></item>
<item><title>Free Microsoft Mathematics</title><description>Free set of mathematical tools for students that'll not only provide the answers but will also teach how to get there with 2D and 3D visualisations.</description><link>http://www.microsoft.com/downloads/en/details.aspx?FamilyID=9caca722-5235-401c-8d3f-9e242b794c3a&displaylang=en</link></item>
<item><title>Free Microsoft Security Essentials</title><description>Highly rated app that'll provide real-time protection for your PC - guarding it from viruses, spyware, and malicious software, and it won't slow your PC down either!</description><link>http://www.microsoft.com/security_essentials/</link></item>
<item><title>Free Lord of Ultima Online Strategy Game</title><description>Build your very own medieval city, trade and ally with players, while spying on, plundering and attacking others... all to become the mighty Lord of Ultima.</description><link>http://www.lordofultima.com/en?a=all4freeuk.co.uk&sourceid=all4freeuk.co.uk</link></item>
<item><title>Free Americas Army 3 PC Game</title><description>Developed by the US Army players are bound by the rules of engagement with teamwork being the key to success in the game.</description><link>http://www.americasarmy.com/downloads/</link></item>
<item><title>Free BattleForge Online Strategy Game</title><description>Combining strategy, fantasy, trading cards, and magical spells, in an online world with exiting campaigns, great characters, and tons of playable cards, all free!</description><link>http://www.battleforge.com/en/home/landingpage.bfg?q=Play4Free_Portal?sourceid=Play4Free_Portal</link></item>
<item><title>Free Battlefield Heroes Online Game</title><description>Join millions for EA's 3rd person cartoon shooter, and enjoy hours of fun in this fast paced, multi-player game, with built in matchmaking to ensure a fair fight.</description><link>http://www.battlefieldheroes.com/</link></item>
<item><title>Free AVG Antivirus</title><description>Award winning software that'll provide protection from viruses, spyware, and other nasties, and with LinkScanner you'll be protected from harmful websites too.</description><link>http://free.avg.com/gb-en/download-avg-anti-virus-free</link></item>
<item><title>Free Autodesk Suite for Students</title><description>Free leading design apps, as used by 9 million designers, engineers, and digital artists, inc. Autodesk Inventor, Revit, 3ds Max, Maya, and AutoCAD.</description><link>http://students.autodesk.com/</link></item>
<item><title>Free Grand Theft Auto Games</title><description>Rockstar is giving away some of their early titles including the original GTA and GTA 2 as well as Wild Metal Country too.</description><link>http://www.rockstargames.com/classics/</link></item>
<item><title>Free Microsoft Money Plus Sunset Editions</title><description>Keep track of all your finances, and manage your income and outgoings better, with this now free edition of the popular Money series which has now sadly ended.</description><link>http://www.microsoft.com/money/sunset.mspx</link></item>
<item><title>Free Kaspersky Security Software</title><description>If you bank online with Barclays you'll be entitled to free PC and Mac security software, and even one for your mobile too, courtesy of Kaspersky Antivirus.</description><link>http://www.barclays.co.uk/Helpsupport/FreeInternetsecuritysoftware/P1242557966961</link></item>
<item><title>Free Microsoft Small Basic Programming Tool</title><description>Use this great free tool as a simple and easy way to get into software development - allowing kids and adults to enjoy producing simple games and apps.</description><link>http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/beginner/ff384126.aspx</link></item>
<item><title>Free Microsoft Software for Students</title><description>Students can get free professional Microsoft products worth £1,000's, including Visual Studio Pro, development tools for Windows Phone, Xbox, and more!</description><link>https://www.dreamspark.com/default.aspx?</link></item>
<item><title>Free Doctor Who Adventure Games</title><description>Battle the Daleks, the Cybermen, and more in these truly impressive looking games from the makers of the new Doctor Who series starring Matt Smith.</description><link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/doctorwho/dw/theadventuregames</link></item>
<item><title>Free Large File Sharing with WeTransfer</title><description>Use WeTransfer to securely share large files of up to 2GB with who ever you want - a perfect alternative for sending them via email.</description><link>https://wetransfer.com/</link></item>
<item><title>Free Serif Software</title><description>Create anything from documents, websites, graphics, panoramas, movies, and more plus photo editing, scrap booking, and others with this free software from Serif.</description><link>http://www.freeserifsoftware.com/</link></item>
<item><title>Free Need for Speed World Online Game</title><description>Online multiplayer action racing game for the PC where you can race with friends or complete against thousands of other players in a seamless open world.</description><link>http://world.needforspeed.com/</link></item>
<item><title>Free Paragon Backup & Recovery</title><description>Highly awarded and based on the commercial version - their free edition will give you a rich set of features that you can trust and ensure your data remains safe!</description><link>http://www.paragon-software.com/home/db-express/index.html</link></item>
<item><title>Free ImgBurn Disc Writer</title><description>An excellent lightweight disc burning app for writing CDs, DVDs, HD-DVDs, Blu-rays and no doubt everything else that'll be developed!</description><link>http://www.imgburn.com/</link></item>
<item><title>Free Railroad Tycoon PC Game</title><description>Enjoy the strategy game that started the whole Tycoon genre and experience a piece of PC gaming history with this classic game.</description><link>http://www.2kgames.com/railroads/railroads.html</link></item>
<item><title>Free Email Archiving & Backup</title><description>Backup all your emails from multiple applications and accounts into a single secure archive with fast search one-click backup and powerful export.</description><link>http://www.mailstore.com/en/mailstore-home.aspx</link></item>
<item><title>Free Legacy Family Tree</title><description>Innovatively pinpoint and plot important locations in your ancestors lives from within the software using Microsoft Virtual Earth... and so much more!</description><link>http://www.legacyfamilytree.com/</link></item>
<item><title>Free Open Office Suite</title><description>Leading open source office suite for word processing, spreadsheets, databases, presentations, graphics, and more that's fully compatible with Microsoft Office.</description><link>http://www.openoffice.org/</link></item>
<item><title>Free Microsoft Express Developer Tools</title><description>Selection of express developer tools including software for web development, Windows 8 apps, desktop apps, Windows Phone apps, and more.</description><link>http://www.microsoft.com/express/</link></item>
<item><title>Free 2GB Dropbox Cloud Storage</title><description>Sync, share, and backup up to 2GB of files of any kind between all your PC's, on the web, and from your mobile, with Dropbox.</description><link>http://www.dropbox.com/</link></item>
<item><title>Free Return to Castle Wolfenstein: Enemy Territory Game</title><description>Play as the Axis or Allies in traditional single scenarios or wage war through a series of linked scenarios in a totally new campaign mode in this classic PC game.</description><link>http://download.cnet.com/Return-to-Castle-Wolfenstein-Enemy-Territory-full-install/3000-7441_4-10243510.html?tag=mncol</link></item>
<item><title>Free Dulux Colour Guide</title><description>Packed full of inspirational ideas for your home this handy guide will help you choose the right colours and products to decorate your home the way you want.</description><link>http://www.dulux.co.uk/colours/samples/guide.jsp</link></item>
<item><title>Free Audiobook worth £20+</title><description>Trial Audible free for 30 days and get to keep an audiobook from their library of 50,000 titles including best selling authors through to well-known classics.</description><link>http://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-505161-10450406</link></item>
<item><title>Free Book Exchange</title><description>Book Crossing is the worlds largest free book exchange with hundreds of thousands of members sharing books in hundreds of countries around the world!</description><link>http://www.bookcrossing.com/</link></item>
<item><title>Free Nature Identification Book</title><description>Help identify the natural world around you and help The Woodland Trust to record the seasonal changes in your local wildlife with this free guide.</description><link>http://www.naturescalendar.org.uk/register</link></item>
<item><title>Free Fine Literature eBooks</title><description>Project Gutenberg has thousands of fine literature books from known authors available to read on every device conceivable inc. iPhone, Android, Kindle, and more.</description><link>http://www.gutenberg.org/</link></item>
<item><title>Free eBooks & Historical Documents</title><description>The Online Books Page has links to over a million ebooks and historical documents in various electronic formats from all over the world.</description><link>http://digital.library.upenn.edu/books/</link></item>
<item><title>Free St John Ambulances First Aid Guides</title><description>Pocket sized guide that covers the five common conditions where straightforward first aid could be the difference between a life lost and a life saved.</description><link>https://www.sja.org.uk/sja/support-us/the-difference/get-a-free-first-aid-guide.aspx</link></item>
<item><title>Free Google Play eBooks</title><description>Free ebooks from classic writers including Jane Austen, Mary Shelley, Hans Christian Andersen, Charles Dickens, and many more besides.</description><link>https://play.google.com/store/books/collection/topselling_free</link></item>
<item><title>Free The Jungle Book Kindle eBook</title><description>Amongst the reams of free ebooks at Amazon you can get this classic gem by author Rudyard Kipling free for Kindle devices – saving you a few quid over the actual book.</description><link>http://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/redirect.html?ie=UTF8&location=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.co.uk%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB000JQU7JO%2Fref%3Dnosim%2F&tag=a4fu-21&linkCode=ur2&camp=1634&creative=6738</link></item>
<item><title>Free Amazon Kindle Books</title><description>If you're a Kindle owner or thinking of becoming one, then this huge collection of free titles, including classics and moderns will be a nice addition to your library.</description><link>http://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/redirect.html?ie=UTF8&location=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.co.uk%2FKindle-Store%2Fs%2Fqid%3D1288111525%3Fie%3DUTF8%26sort%3Dprice%26rh%3Dn%253A341677031%252Cn%253A%2521341678031%252Cn%253A341689031%26page%3D1&tag=a4fu-21&linkCode=ur2&camp=1634&creative=6738</link></item>
<item><title>Free Comic Books</title><description>Every year on a day in May comic book stores across the world give away loads of free comics - just pop down to your local store to collect yours.</description><link>http://www.freecomicbookday.com/Home/1/1/27/992</link></item>
<item><title>Free Digital Comics</title><description>Comixology has loads of free issues of popular comics including Batman, Wonder Woman, Green Lantern, Joker, Superman, and more.</description><link>http://www.comixology.com/free-comics</link></item>
<item><title>Free Wartime Farm Booklet</title><description>The Open University is giving away free copies of their booklet to accompany the TV series about how the war affected agriculture.</description><link>http://www.open.edu/openlearn/whats-on/tv/order-your-free-wartime-farm-booklet</link></item>
<item><title>Free Scrabble Player's Handbook</title><description>Download this free eBook from the world's best Scrabble tournament players – and maybe you'll be better in Words with Friends or Alphajax too!</description><link>http://www.scrabbleplayershandbook.com/</link></item>
<item><title>Free Library eBooks & Audiobooks</title><description>Lots of libraries across the UK are joining the digital revolution and are now lending out eBooks and audiobooks directly online.</description><link>http://search.overdrive.com/</link></item>
<item><title>Free Icons of Wales Booklet</title><description>The Open University is giving away free copies of this booklet that celebrates eleven prominent figures in Welsh history.</description><link>http://www.open.edu/openlearn/history-the-arts/history/heritage/get-your-free-icons-wales-booklet</link></item>
<item><title>Free Star Gazing Guide</title><description>The Open University is giving away this free handy pocket sized guide that'll help you discover some amazing facts about the objects in the night sky.</description><link>http://www.open.edu/openlearn/whats-on/tv/order-your-free-star-guide</link></item>
<item><title>Free Go the F**k to Sleep Audiobook</title><description>The frankly hilarious bedtime book that's strictly for the parents is now in audiobook format and comically narrated by none other than Samuel L Jackson!</description><link>http://www.dpbolvw.net/click-990216-10449428?url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.audible.co.uk%2Fpd%3Fasin%3DB0056ABAM6</link></item>
<item><title>Free Dorling Kindersley Books</title><description>Sign up to Club DK for a chance to review their latest books every month and you get to keep your review copy too!</description><link>http://clkuk.tradedoubler.com/click?p(1325)a(793574)url(http://www.dorlingkindersley-uk.co.uk/static/html/features/clubdk/index.html)</link></item>
<item><title>Free Mills & Boon Books</title><description>Join the Mills & Boon book club now and they'll send you two free books and a mystery gift too - plus you can keep your freebies and pay absolutely nothing!</description><link>http://www.awin1.com/awclick.php?mid=1150&id=3927&p=http://www.millsandboon.co.uk/2freebooks.asp</link></item>
<item><title>Two Free Audiobooks worth £40!</title><description>Sign up for a 30 day trial of Audible and enjoy two free audiobooks that you can keep even if you cancel including The Casual Vacancy by J. K. Rowling and many more!</description><link>http://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-990216-10449428?url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.audible.co.uk%2Ft1%2FATV-TVJULY%3Fsource_code%3DATV30DFT2Bk0003OT062912</link></item></channel></rss>